So they write and chichimene tension.
I think it's very good that when you're
teaching meditation, it's a group to
remind everyone of
72 things you've heard me say
many times. My first teacher in 1702,
173, before you were born, he would take out
a pencil and break it, and then he would take out
ten pencils and you couldn't see them.
When we meditate, they are like days of pencils,
they are much stronger,
and when people meditate alone, they are
weaker. So a group can be very
powerful and can help you. But
what's the problem with meditating in a
group?
Someone makes
yang noise, and the word for healing
in Tibetan,
the word for enemy, is the same
word.
I'm
joking that sound is the
enemy of meditation. So when
you teach a group of people,
the pencil comes first, and then it's
not good to talk about positive things and
then tell them, "If you move in this
meditation, you're going to distract
everyone, you're going to take them out of their meditation." So you must
be extremely quiet
during your group meditation and have a
place for yourself. If you move,
you...  Mind Justin, uff, your mind moves, your
meditation, I am, bring them, they want,
so you must get into the habit of
sitting like a statue, like sending
this seed, 65 every second they open, and we
all have a mixture of good
seeds and bad seeds, that's why we
're still here in this typical world,
we're the stupid kids in class
who never made it to the
next level,
so if we're still here
we have good seeds and bad footprints,
otherwise we wouldn't be here, we'd be somewhere else,
so as you meditate more the
seeds will open too, and you'll
feel something, something will happen, a fly will sting,
your nose will start to hurt like you've
never had before, you're going to think about
your high school sweetheart, that we've
thought about in 30 years, even your forehead hurt,
something's going to happen,
so a big part of
meditation is just being tough, jealous,
strong,
these seeds are going to show, and nobody
has a perfect meditation, you
think I have it but I don't, you
think the person who's with you has it, they don't either, so you have to
fight this
artist, you have to be strong,
don't move,
the boyfriend comes for half an hour, try to
cut him off again  Don't give up on your life.
We've talked about the three editing goals,
and this big one: how many
looked at the stars yesterday
in this market? In the world,
we had the moon yesterday, and not from Vigo, it's
the great hermitage of Asia. It's about
helping billions of planets,
and there was a... never... the arms... if you don't
meditate, and you will die without knowing what is
happening in the world.
Okay, the ephemeral one who doesn't have many
immediate options... you will see these things, and it
will change you forever, and never stop.
And then you will become a fanatic, a
non-fanatic, a
master, a non-fanatic. There is that on the
journey,
and it would be a shame if you didn't see these
things there. They have life because you can...
alone if you don't want to sit and meditate.
So your phone is very important,
which is very important, and it's very important that... what is
Ponzi? A lunar... Russian
churros? Because this word is in every
language
because they are important things, yes, but to
see billions of planets and millions of
beings and love them all... to have that
experience once in your life,
and it's worth it. So let's
try it,
and the meditation that we are going to have
connects with...  The teaching we're going to
have in the next section is about hunger, and we're going to have our
eyes closed.
If you're sleepy and you try to meditate in the
afternoon, you can open your eyes a little, just a little,
but don't look at anything. It's
useless to meditate facing
something. It's
useful to meditate on something in front of
a wall that's a single
color. If you choose to meditate with your
eyes open,
that will prevent you from being present
and make you...
They say to pay attention to
something, but it doesn't mean you should do physical exercises. It does
n't mean you should look at the tip of an
eyebrow. If that area of ​​your nose
means you should focus on
relaxing your eyes, they don't move at a distance. I don't
have...
so you can experience that. You can try to
open your eyes,
but don't pay attention.
Matthei, you feel it's important that when they
teach meditation, every time people
relax, they relax their face. It's very
natural.
Mind focus is when the mind focuses.
Time is when we
learn... our face,
especially our brow,
and time... before... 3. It's very
important. I found that this place...
this book of wrinkles...
so check the place where
your eyebrows are...
that it's not tense in the area
and another place where we always
get tense is in the knees of
our mouth so relax the
corners of your mouth to the activist to the one from
the manuals is I like to say that
you put a little Mona Lisa smile
efe is my little love cornerstone on
the 2nd anniversary
the ida and ping channels to the ones
next to your chip analysis if you do
that they will relax and your meditation
will be better
check your fingers are they
clenched are tense or are they
relaxed
in this teacher's gender
there are generally two ways to hold your stomach
you can take the natural and naturally
of slightly you can't is the clench and
squeeze it a little very little
and if you have this habit of clenching
your stomach muscles a little I did
n't make any stop when
sitting meditation uninstall back he
will relax his lower back
runs panistas relax the
corresponding muscles in the back of the
body
I
in the shoulders are a place of
very great tension in the human being
and mar experiment instagram you could
experiment that instead of putting your
hands on your knees you
can see them
Pulling your shoulders back a little is between your
thighs, and that will open your shoulders.
If one of your shoulders is more tense
than the other, almost all humans—
and be aware that we are both right- and left-handed—so
generally one arm
is more tense than the other, and this tension
bends your spine.
So try to keep your shoulders
even and press them back a little,
just a little. It's easier if you
pull your hands back a little towards your
thighs. So if you have your hands
on your knees, there's a tendency for
the shadows to tense up.
In yoga,
yoga is of the type that this is why it's
the law itself.
As much as you can have a
yoga session, it affects your thinking and affects how
you move. Experiment. So you can
experiment with it
even with your eyes closed.
Where are you putting your eyes
after the city?
So you have an application.
You can look down
with your eyes closed, but when the
mind tends to darken and feel the
way that makes you sleepy, and if you look very
upwards, it
will move the prana in a way that
agitates
lively. So if  You look from above the
horizon,
driving as if you were driving
and you're seeing something, the distance, Ajax
light, and if your eyes are a little
higher than the level, you'll realize that it
takes a while, like a positive. So
in yoga, not even merit, in
meditation, 45 different closed positions, there's
a very big difference, and
free, and you leave your eyes a little raised.
The one, Jack and Steve, is the one. I
know that again, the last time, if your face
is relaxed, your hands are relaxed,
and your stomach is just hanging, it's a
little tight. I
activate them and start, or check it one last
time before starting to meditate.
Look for where the attention is: in the mouth,
in the leaves,
between the eyebrows,
endemic, that ask for protection. And now
we go to the last breath. It's a
tradition where we inhabit, cohesion
of life, better so that you
start to
look at your breath. In Genoa,
it clarified that in principle it seems like love to us.
Generally, it's good. You can
breathe through your nose, but if you have a
cold or it's difficult, it's okay to
breathe through your mouth
while you breathe through your nose. A
trick that you can do, which is
when trying to carry the  Breathing a
little higher, of
course, still through
natural nasal breathing, but directing the air
through these slightly
higher nostrils helps you focus.
Directing the air a little higher,
a little higher in the head,
opens cavities that provide more
oxygen.
Traditionally, you count 10 breaths, and it's
very important to start with the
exhalation.
There's extra air in your lungs,
oxygenated and unused, and it's
worthwhile. If you're going to meditate
successfully,
it's important to exhale all the air.
When you breathe, the system... So,
during these breaths, we're going to
take this opportunity
to confirm that we're exhaling
all the air into the lungs. Naturally, they'll
hold their
breath
after the exhalation and for a little
while after the inhalation. So,
during the setup for a
successful, gentle meditation,
the lungs will stop after
the exhalation. So, try to
consciously push in a little more air. And reading is about
being aware of your breathing because it's
automatic; we generally don't think
about it.
So, while meditating, the material will be much
better in your meditation if you learn...  to
get all the air out, all the extra anger that
stays in your lungs,
the exhalation. So I like to tell
people not to worry too much about the
inhalation, your body will take care of
those automatic things. And look at zinc, and if
you have to think about it, if
we had to think about the inhalation we'd already be
dead. So don't
worry about the inhalation,
but I am very aware of the exhalation.
You arrive another day that says it's long
and thin,
demonstrate that English.
So let's start counting the
access breaths
on the exhalation. Today's exhalation,
the inhalation stops counting the
exhalations. 2
today, Iniesta, and the tradition is that
you count to 10. Careful, I have and design
without thinking about anything else. I'm going to
quote, so the mental spiders
are going to be opening up, rights defenders,
since 65 per second here,
the sixth.
So maintaining your 65 miles per
second thinking about the exhalation is
practically impossible for the
human being. Pursuing, pinching, and gold
in general, you can think about the
breathing.
It's about starting to turn off the
outside world. Here we go, 10 breaths.  And
traditionally,
if you get to 5s, your high school boyfriend
comes back to your mind,
then supposedly you have to start
again, and if you're very honest with yourself, you'll
probably never get to your
meditations. It's just that you only try it
a few times.
Excel, when you exhale properly,
the plan to which Ana flows better in your
body,
and it doesn't give you Tyler's link. The link
means help, that the air that
accumulates, cassette of focus, next
main,
because your mind starts to affect your
heart, you feel nervous, nervous, already
distracted, the champion ended up with a
special headache, which is a
headache, in the end. So if you take medication and you
get these strong symptoms
in Saint Marc,
like anxiety, in the heart, like a
pain in the heart, with
other fingers start to tremble, and you
feel agitated by the meditation,
this type, you can fix most of
these problems just by exhaling well,
properly throughout
your meditation. So that's a very
good solution for these
nervous problems that come from meditating for a long
time, and if you don't solve it
properly, it's going to get worse and worse.
Long, happy, and mindful installations,
sharp la  My face is soft in Wizards Art, my
fingers so soft, my stomach isn't soft,
so relaxed, my eyes... I
worked 19 years in Manhattan at a
diamond company in my area, and
we had our boss at the company, she was
a woman.
Usually, she was agitated or
angry. There was
a company joke, I
think she was the only one who didn't know
about the joke.
We had about 800 people in the
building,
and outside her office, you'd find out what
people were asking her. How's the
weather? Can you give me a weather report? It was
a joke that meant if
she was in a good mood,
people would say, "I heard on the radio, I might go
see that guy arrived today." It
was a way for
all the employees to say, "Do
n't go to her office right now."
So, let's take a weather report.
Close to my own mind,
how I look this morning, and did I sleep well?
Michalak is doing well,
and how is my mental climate
this morning before we start
meditating? After the breathing,
we're going to take a defined role, shrinking the
climate, our mind, and the... last a few
minutes in this.  Relax, have fun,
fill with rhythm, check your mind and see
how the weather is, how your mind is
this morning, how peaceful my mind is.
A couple of minutes, you might think about
other things,
that's part of the weather report, so
come back and see
how your mind is this morning, what
your mind has, don't try to
do anything, I want to play and live, just
try to have a weather report,
the hunger theme, the steps for
agent illumination, locate this
session this week, and Scott Gration
called arrow, it's a Sanskrit word,
an English word,
it's a plant you can see here
and it has thorns
in the leaves, they prick your hand like a
cactus, but they are sharp.
If you hold the commander's leaves, they
prick, they don't make a wound, but they leave you with
some
discomfort. To
acquire comfort about
clay is a negative thought in your
mind, a negative thought, and not
necessarily, and we're going to study it for a
week
in this definition, in the definition of
the class,
7 cents,
the Ford is a thought of mind that goes
to your mind in Wii Sisters and that  It disturbs
the mind, your peace of mind. The peace of mind of
the person who has it is like the weather
in the central-eastern air, very, very quiet and
calm.
The wind may begin to blow. You can
think of the surface of a lake;
that is the natural state
of the mind. The natural state of your mind is like
a very quiet lake,
and the surface of the water is like a
mirror.
And in the morning, after the sun comes up, like
the ocean, and that's what we call it, it's
like how glass swirls today
because the sun hasn't warmed it up yet. And then,
90, 79,
we go like glass. That is
the natural state of a clear mind.
When a negative emotion comes,
then it disturbs all the water.
You have waves in your mind, waves in the water. It ca
n't be.
Let's do an experiment this morning,
and then we're going to take a break. We're not
going to do it for very long.
So, take the weather of your mind, the
input of the normal weather, and usually, your
mind is like glass.
If you slept well, usually in the
morning,
the mind is calm, neutral,
smooth. That's why the morning is a
good time to meditate because the mind
is naturally softer,
so we think of things...  Those of us who
have to do all day,
we start thinking about the challenges of
our lives before, so we're going to do
an experiment this morning in
Honda Classic Focus. We're going to focus on
our mind, so it's like
smooth glass. Before you go,
without
studies on paper and the purpose,
we're going to bring one
for less
and I'm going to help you ruin your step in
total, so here we go. Focus on the
main elf 15 in your mind of insight,
stay inside,
choose,
and it's quiet,
the water is calm, class like
smooth glass, and enjoy
city 7
of the calm of class
disaster, which is like glass for a
few minutes.
This mosque is in the stomach, it's
a little tight in the rest,
the inhalations are still a little
higher in your head, faces, in short,
wizards of the sun, the head and fingers are still
without tension, there is the coach, the
exhalations are still conscious,
once it's
not bad,
the mind relaxed
as if it were glass
naturally,
try not to move because when we
move we distract people, we
disturb them,
nothing.
Now, possibly for the first time in your
life,
we are going to purposely cause a storm in
the mind of Sutter
By the way, we're going to say we're
only going to disrupt one live stream, so everyone in
life, every Holy Week, is going to cause some
media challenge. Barça, do you have any challenge?
Possibly someone in your life, well, let them know that there are
some because of an
obvious situation. Maybe it's a
situation
at your house.
Think of
the blind woman.
Maybe it's a problem with your wife. Or
the people you work with.
In this role, I
would like them to vote. By the way, go to
an uncomfortable place.
Classic ruin. I exist.
See more of the peaceful water in the middle of a
long corridor with the agriculture. Now we're going to
do a meditation. I have a
current report.
Mental concentration means
focusing on something. It's something.
Focus on something that's bothering you. It was
a guy who was always
different from the one who causes problems,
and at the moment, he seems less important,
and then you can't remember anything.
What's your
para Webber?
What's your bad weather?
This week, this month, who's giving you
problems?
Ned Flanders.
And we're going to focus on Stroeder's message,
and we're going to destroy our peace of mind.
We're going to bring a storm with wind
across this lake. You start
thinking about breakfast in the
good quality deserves to return your focus we
are not meditating our hand
we are meditating in the middle to see
how we are medical and someone who
really irritates me
is a list of all the things that
tend to bother you
don't stop there
must be more things that irritate you
and now I return from the breath
observers science the action three
long exhalations
at once don't open your eyes don't
move I have lost
maintain your discipline in meditation
until the last moment
of instaure or diapers
is athletic that if slowly stretch out
of questions the meditation
I would like to take a long break so you
have to go to the bathroom just
go maybe I will go
the intermittent tax and we will ask
them some questions I have
Joe's phone
you will choose is it's his fault if he doesn't
choose you
good morning I already
have a question
very good try again
the person who bothers me was actually
myself
and I try to think of someone else
then you need have to I should
focus
but also if you are what
irritates you the most then you are seeing then that
the problem Father Cross or think that it
could also be a situation it could
be the weather of Lemon Mountain it
could be the hot water that not  It makes
sense,
Emery Take-Two Bath, so the point
of the meditation is to observe a believer
if we want to see that kind of thing that makes me feel good,
since it makes me feel good
because all our lives we've had
minors every hour, but we never realize what we
do, what they do to us,
how it disturbs our minds. It says that in
this meditation, Joe, your goal is to find
something that screams at you.
So if it's a problem to find something
that irritates you, you're a very
special person, but thinking about yourself is
fine, water, and you fall. So I want
you to observe the kind of punishment
that the church does to you because you've
had it all your life, me too,
but we don't realize it. Have they made us
aware of what it does to us? Any other
questions?
Thank you for the meditation. Making minute, I was
wondering if you could clarify where to
breathe when it says higher up on the
head. Yes, that's
something I've been
working on. When you teach this, it's a
teacher training. It's
a very rich source of things we
talk about. It's been brought down into yourself. You can
share with your students some
discoveries you've made yourself, and
in my opinion
as a teacher
Be more passionate and more interesting
for these students if you talk about your
own problems, your own challenges,
honestly.
If you've been working on
something this week, bring it to your
class. I find my way to bring it out in
your class because we all have more passion. I just got
back from China with a
headache, and then I was thinking about
traveling. Van Slyke, you have like
little hells
in your mind, your nasal cavities.
Can you avoid them, or can you
consciously... In some of
their texts, they tell you that the palate is a
very important part of the body. There are
whole schools of yoga
that say that the word is very important,
and I'm very curious about that. So
I'm just trying.
I think if your nasal cavities
are totally clear, and if I
'm consciously collecting them, it's going to
affect your parana up here.
Sometimes just coughing, and students
are doing this. I think there's something
there. I'm still not sure, and it's more
fun for everyone.
So I'm just working on it.
Any other questions?
And I do believe that oxygen will also reach
the brain, but try it.
Thank you,
and mark Font. You ask me about the
body specifically.
If someone has chronic pain, and I want  To
teach,
if you want to teach people with chronic pain,
how can you be mentally if you can't
be comfortable in your body?
How can you adjust to this?
So the question is, if
chronic pain is like pain that doesn't go away in
your back or your hips,
pain that seems to stay with you for a
long time,
then right now they are learning to be
less. You can always drive a
response. They have two levels, and you don't have to
touch them.
And Merida,
and I can tell you that things—
this is one of the levels—or I can go
into those seeds that are
causing your pain. I, who you are,
maintain today in a good moment of my
life,
Bradford, and 40 to 45 years of
teaching, as a teacher, to help
answer, mix the two deep answers.
Work on your seeds because it will
tell you if Zelaya is chronically protective.
Imagine if, in my opinion, an
effective response in the area should
mix the two in the
superficial answers, at the surface level, and
at the deep level,
I try to connect them because in the end,
opium was created by your karma too, and
Seremi by your seed.
That's classic.
The superficial causes also come
from deep things.  Connect them
when that's how I would work on both
levels. Number one, a
whole system to help your body: how you eat, how you
feel, if you do some
exercise every day, and all that. These are
things we do here. We're going to do
yoga after meditation.
The older people do it every day. They
come every day. He just got
back because he traveled the world
three times a year last month, and he's
70, 71.
One of my doctors, I checked him
not too long ago, told me I have the
healthiest body he's ever seen,
and it's just from practicing.
He tried to get rid of a distraction,
and now we're going to assign. I don't have to
do my meditation
before. I think, you
know, a normal, relaxed habit of
stretching every day. We have a program on
the balcony, and it's run by
Mexico. Some of it is so old
because we had permission from Congress to
teach our stuff to 23 million
children. Maybe the biggest thing we
've ever done is
trading. So we've been
struggling to find a guy for
the program, and we already have 23 names,
and the name, or the last name,
Yasky
Soy Stick Wing is the Verín, and that's where
the stretching comes in.  Green, so
green, all the
green drinks, stretching, it's not serious, yoga is
for Hindus,
so I'm just talking about your body every
day and deep in the pen from the store in
the seeds, the whole program for 23
million children is green, stretch with
those three green things, throw pen, take
a green group every day in the
morning,
and it really does something for you, it tastes very
bad
[Laughs].
Every day
we had a yoga class before coming
here that's being called...
we have all kinds of people in the class,
and well, you don't always have to stand on your
head, some have operations,
just stretch
those superficial things in the green and
stretch, and then the other pen,
so it helps other people who have
chronic pain, if it really works, don't do it
in an easy and quick way,
pick a person who has
chronic pain and become their chronic pain friend
and talk about chronic pain,
green juice recipes, just go back to the
topic-free zone, don't visit it every
two weeks, that's what I tell them, I was telling them
because they're not serious and it doesn't say that it's
a resource for them, someone,
so if the prey on your scanner is
The person who is going to help them with their
chronic pain, ask them about it.
We have some people within
the group, and possibly their
hand was cut off. They hurt themselves, so they are
always carrying it, and she
is very busy.
She is trying to divide,
manage a retreat. She is very
busy, but still, she tries to be
responsible for this person. I don't know, I
am very busy, I am very busy, but
this investment is needed, and no one else
wants to do it because the person is very
large.
So don't let the person go, don't let
your green drink go,
and don't let your daily stretching
go. Some kind of stretching, even if you ca
n't do yoga,
then find a person you
can link to, and be the person
who takes care of them. Many deep causes
and causes without a profile. You already know which is
the deep one, which are the
superficial ones.
[Music]
In this sense, it
will work with someone. It stays in
the hands of the people because there is one
more question.
[Music]
Thank you, teacher. Until the second time
I am at Diamond Mountain, and when I try
to meditate, my left eye
starts to cry. Always tears
in my left eye. What can I do about
that?
Sad tears, happy tears, or
just water?  It's
a mix of everything,
happy and sad.
So I kept telling them that
I'm an older man and I've seen a lot of
things in my sanity, and that generally,
the Roman saint said that their tears are very
precious like pearls. So if you
can cry sometimes, it's a very good
sign. It's a very good thing. Happy,
sad, they're pearls,
like precious pearls, like pearls. Felix
means that you have feelings and that
you care about people,
so I think it's a beautiful thing
everywhere. So just drink a lot of water.
We're in the desert here, you can't waste
water.
[Music]
Alright, we're going to break, and we're going
to take an official 15-
minute break to come back at 85. I'm going to
start at 85, and if our horse matters to me